









# Hello! I'm Phillip

A self-taught full-stack web developer and graphic designer from Fort Worth, Texas.

I worked as a lead designer for eight years in San Francisco and two years in Hawaii for the same company then moved back to Texas in the summer of 2015 and started working for American Airlines.

In 2020, I began my journey to a full-stack web developer when AA demoted half the workforce to part-time which fueled my resolve to becoming a software engineer.

Since then, I have been designing and developing web applications using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, and SQL. Currently, I am learning and building web applications with C# / ASP .NET and MVC.

Thank you for taking the time to read this and I look forward to hearing from and working with you.

# **WORK EXPERIENCES**

### Online Self-Paced Student

CoderFoundry.com / From 2021 to Present

A self-paced Online course that focuses on building web applications using HTML, CSS and JavaScript, C#, ASP .Net MVC.

#### Fleet Service Agent

American Airlines/ From 2015 to 2023

I perform the handling and transporting of items on and off aircraft, carts, containers, and trucks between terminals and aircraft; receiving, delivering, weighing and documenting cargo for a specific facility (warehouse) or a loading dock area. Push-back qualified for movement of aircraft to and from different terminals and gates.

#### Lead Designer

Robert Noble Interior Design/ From 2005 to 2015

Assisted in maintaining and enhancing website for Mr. Noble by keeping up with modern trends for the benefit of his clients. I worked hand in hand with photographers to showcase the handmade furniture that was being produced in Italy. I managed small teams as an art director to develop the proper coherence for a particular design and also focused on creating templates for future projects.

### **EDUCATION**

### **BFA - Communication Design**

Texas Tech University | Lubbock, TX 2001 - 2005

#### **ADDY Award Winner**

Gold - State Silver - Nat i ona 2005

## **SKILLS**

Illustrator

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

Bootstrap

SQL

C#

ASP.Net

 $\mathsf{MVC}$